Sella Rafaeli, CV: Full-Stack Developer

American Citizen, currently living in Israel (Dec 2017) sella.rafaeli@gmail.com, https://sellarafaeli.com

Skills

I have +15 years of experience of full-stack web development and management; backend, frontend, product. Ex-8200, HUJI, Fiverr.

I am an expert in web development, including Ruby (Rails, Sinatra), Python (Flask, Django), JavaScript ('Vanilla', Vue, React, Angular1, Angular2+, Node), AWS/Heroku, DBs such as MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Redis, and similar.

Education

OCT 2009 - JUL 2012

Hebrew University, Jerusalem - BSc Computer Science, graduated Magna Cum Laude

JUL 2008

786 / 800 on Israeli's SAT (National Psychometric Exam), top 0.01%.

Experience

APRIL 2016 - PRESENT

Full-Stack Web Team Leader, Team8

- Hands-on development and team leadership of enterprise BE web server (mostly Ruby and MongoDB).
- Hands-on development and team leadership of enterprise FE web app (mostly Angular2+).

MARCH 2015 - APRIL 2016

Founder & CTO, yes.no

- Founder, CTO, recruited and managed R&D team of 6.
- Crowd-Interviewing Platform
- Raised 1M\$. Sold, private.

2012 - MARCH 2015

Senior Full-Stack Web Developer, Fiverr

- Led development on banking, payment and order flows
- Led development on Innovation Team

2009 - 2012

Hebrew University, BSc Computer Science

• Graduated Magna Cum Laude

• Minor in Psychology

2003 - 2008

IDF, 8200

- Intelligence Officer; please ask for references.
- Receiver of multiple IDF awards.

Published Works

- My published articles: https://sellarafaeli.com/blog/
- My e-book on Linear Algebra: https://sites.google.com/site/linearitɪhujibook/
- My e-book on Algorithms: https://sites.google.com/site/linearit1hujibook/see-also
- My e-book on Git: https://sellarafaeli.wordpress.com/2014/03/23/git-sandbox-book/